Guide to the Vice President for Student Affairs records, 1923-[ongoing] UA.09.02.0002
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Accession A91-69, 8
  - Student Affairs Reorganization, 1974-1979; 2 folders (Box 95)
  - Student Affairs: Reports to President Sanford (1-4 of 5), 1983-1985; 4 folders (Box 194)
  - Student Affairs: Reports to President Sanford (5 of 5), 1983-1985 (Box 195)
  - Student Affairs Staff Meetings: Agenda, 1979-1986 (Box 95)
  - Student Affairs Staff: Correspondence, 1981-1986 (Box 95)
  - Student Affairs Staff Meetings: Minutes (1 of 2), 1979-1986 (Box 95)
  - Student Affairs Staff Meetings: Minutes (2 of 2), 1979-1986 (Box 96)
  - Student Affairs: Flowers Renovations, 1980-1981 (Box 96)
  - Student Affairs: Organizational Charts, 1980 (Box 96)
  - Student Affairs Survey: Undergraduate Residential Life, 1980 (Box 96)
  - Student Affairs Year-End Report, 1981 (Box 96)
  - Student Alumni Relations Committee (SARC), 1982-1985 (Box 96)
  - Student Committee for Institutional Advancement & Alumni Affairs, 1980 (Box 96)
  - Student Emergencies, 1972-1985; 2 folders (Box 195)
  - Student Locator Service, 1976-1981 (Box 96)
  - Student Projects, 1977-1985 (Box 96)
  - Student Leaders Questionnaire, 1979-1980 (Box 96)
  - Summer Program Planning, 1981-1983 (Box 96)
  - Summer Theater Program Committee, 1981-1984 (Box 97)
  - Task Force for Academic Space Utilization, 1985; 3 folders (Box 97)
  - Task Force to Evaluate Residential System, 1984 (Box 97)
  - Task Force on Residence Hall Renovations, 1981 (Box 97)
  - Tel-Com/Telephones, 1981-1985 (Box 97)
  - Transportation Services, 1981-1987 (Box 97)
  - Triangle Drug Alliance Advisory Board, 1976-1978 (Box 97)
  - The Trent Room, 1985 (Box 97)
  - Trinity College, Committee on Educational Policy (Burian), 1980-1982 (Box 97)
  - Trumpet, 1988-1991 (Box 97)
  - Undergraduate Faculty Council: Academic Standards Committee, 1974-1985 (Box 97)
  - Undergraduate Faculty Council: Admissions and Financial Aid, 1975-1984 (Box 97)
  - Undergraduate Faculty Council: Curriculum Committee, 1972-1986 (Box 98)
  - Undergraduate Faculty Council: Ad hoc Committee on Judicial Policy and Procedures, 1980-1985 (Box 98)
  - Undergraduate Judicial Board: Correspondence, 1979-1986; 2 folders (Box 195)
    FERPA restricted until 2056.
  - Undergraduate Judicial Board: Correspondence, 1971-1979; 3 folders (Box 196)
    FERPA restricted until 2049.
  - United Duke Students, 1980 (Box 98)
  - University Self-Study: Accreditation Committee, 1975-1989; 2 folders (Box 98)
  - University Union: Correspondence, 1981-1986 (Box 98)
  - University Union: Union ReUnion, 1991 (Box 98)
  - Bryan University Center, 1981-1985 (Box 98)
  - Bryan University Center: Planning Committee/Opening, 1981-1982; 3 folders (Box 99)
  - Bryan University Center: Planning Committee/Opening: Minutes, 1981-1982 (Box 99)
  - User's Committee: New Residence Hall (1 of 2), 1982-1984 (Box 99)
  - User's Committee: New Residence Hall (2 of 2), 1982-1984 (Box 100)
  - Vigil, 1968-1988 (Box 100)
    Consists primarily of materials related to the Vigil Anniversary Reunion in 1988, with some correspondence regarding Vigils held in 1981 and narrative recounting the events of 1968 Vigil from an administrator's perspective. A copy of the Duke Chronicle from 1968 April 29 has been removed for digitization and preservation.
  - Washington Post/Time Fellows Program, 1985-1988 (Box 100)
  - Nancy Hanks Memorial, 1983 (Box 100)
    Folder was originally titled "White Duchy"
  - Year-Round Operation (Proposed), 1980 (Box 100)
  - Associated Students of Duke University (ASDU), 1967-1984 (Box 100)
  - ASDU: Correspondence (1-3 of 4), 1981-1982; 3 folders (Box 100)
  - ASDU: Correspondence (4 of 4), 1981-1982 (Box 101)
  - ASDU Drug Policy, 1971 (Box 101)
  - ASDU: Legislation/Minutes, 1988-1989 (Box 101)
  - ASDU: Legislation/Minutes, 1987-1988; 2 folders (Box 101)
  - ASDU: Legislation/Minutes (1 of 3), 1986-1987 (Box 101)
  - ASDU: Legislation/Minutes (2-3 of 3), 1986-1987; 2 folders (Box 102)
  - ASDU: Legislation/Minutes, 1985-1986; 2 folders (Box 102)
  - ASDU: Legislation/Minutes (1 of 2), 1984-1985 (Box 102)
  - ASDU: Legislation/Minutes (2 of 2), 1984-1985 (Box 103)
  - ASDU Quad Committee, 1982 (Box 103)
  - ASDU: Student Studies and Evaluations at Duke University, 1971-1972 (Box 103)
  - Duke Chapel: Correspondence, 1981-1985; 2 folders (Box 103)
  - Duke Chapel: The Brown Foundation, 1972-1973 (Box 103)
  - Duke Chapel: Chapel Music (formerly Choral Activities), 1982-1985 (Box 103)
  - Publications Board: Agendas and Announcements of Meetings, 1982-1985 (Box 103)
  - Publications Board: Contracts, undated (Box 103)
  - Publications Board: Controversies, 1975-1983 (Box 104)
  - Publications Board: Executive Committee, 1969-1984 (Box 104)
  - Publications Board: Membership Lists, 1970-1985 (Box 104)
  - Publications Board: Minutes, 1983-1984 (Box 196)
    FERPA restricted until 2054.
  - Publications Board: Minutes, 1982-1983 (Box 196)
    FERPA restricted until 2053.
  - Publications Board: Minutes, 1981-1982 (Box 196)
    FERPA restricted until 2052.
  - Publications Board: Minutes, 1980-1981 (Box 196)
    FERPA restricted until 2051.
  - Summer Publications Board: Minutes, 1980 (Box 197)
  - Publications Board: Minutes, 1979-1980; 2 folders (Box 197)
  - Summer Publications Board: Minutes, 1979 (Box 197)
  - Publications Board: Minutes, 1978-1979 (Box 197)
  - Summer Publications Board: Minutes, 1978 (Box 197)
  - Publications Board: Minutes, 1977-1978 (Box 197)
  - Summer Publications Board: Minutes, 1977 (Box 197)
  - Publications Board: Minutes, 1976-1977 (Box 198)
  - Summer Publications Board: Minutes, 1976 (Box 198)
    FERPA restricted until 2046.
  - Publications Board: Minutes, 1975-1976 (Box 198)
  - Publications Board: Minutes, 1974-1975 (Box 198)
  - Publications Board: Minutes, 1973-1974 (Box 198)
  - Publications Board: Student Survey, 1971-1977 (Box 104)
  - Publications Board: Journalistic Ethics & Defamatory Communications, undated (Box 104)
  - Publications Board: Obscenity in Press, 1968-1969 (Box 104)
  - Publications Board: "Vulgarity Code", 1970 (Box 104)
  - Publications Board: Relationship with ASDU, 1972 (Box 104)
  - Publications Board: Study Committee, 1970-1971 (Box 104)
  - Chronicle: Correspondence, 1981-1985; 2 folders (Box 104)
  - Chronicle: Circulation, undated (Box 104)
    Contains guides to writing for the Chronicle only.
  - Chronicle: Committee to Study Business Operations, 1970-1972 (Box 104)
  - Chronicle Enterprise System, 1970-1972 (Box 105)
  - Chronicle: Summer Issues, 1970-1971 (Box 105)
  - Chronicle/Administration Relationship Study, 1969-1970 (Box 105)
  - Nova University, Evaluation of, 1977; 4 folders (Box 105)
  - Student Health Service: Correspondence, 1981-1985; 2 folders (Box 105)
  - Student Health Programs: Other Universities, 1969-1983 (Box 106)
  - Student Health Services: Health Services for Women, 1969-1978 (Box 106)
  - Student Health Service Questionnaire: Undergraduate and Graduate, 1979 (Box 106)
  - Student Health Service Questionnaire: Other Universities, 1975-1976; 2 folders (Box 106)
  - Summary File: Subcommittee on the University Union of the Duke University Educational Facilities Committee copy 2 of 3, 1970; 2 folders (Box 106)
- Accession A93-35, 10
  This series includes materials from William Griffith's time as Vice President for Student Affairs. Files are partially alphabetical and include correspondence, reports, memorandums, printed materials, and other materials related to residential life, an AIDS task force, the development of the Mary Lou Williams Center, student insurance, a group of heads of Student Affairs at universities across the country called the Vice Presidents Group, and other topics.
  - AIDS, 1985-1990; 2 folders (Box 107)
  - AIDS Task Force (1-2 of 3), 1986-1990; 2 folders (Box 107)
  - AIDS Task Force (3 of 3), 1986-1990 (Box 108)
  - Angier B. Duke Scholarships, 1972-1989 (Box 108)
  - ASDU Correspondence, 1984-1990 June; 4 folders (Box 108)
  - ASDU Budget and Funding, 1984-1985 (Box 108)
  - ASDU: Information, Charters, 1962-1990 (Box 109)
  - ASDU Legislation/minutes, 1989-1990 (Box 109)
  - ASDU Legislation/minutes, 1990-1991; 2 folders (Box 109)
  - ASDU Resolutions, 1968-1989; 2 folders (Box 109)
  - Association Of Collegiate Entrepreneurs (ACE), 1988 (Box 110)
  - Athletic Department: Users Committee, 1984-1986 (Box 110)
  - Black Affairs, President's Council on: Agenda, 1976-1990 September (Box 110)
  - Black Affairs, President's Council on: Membership, 1976-1990 (Box 110)
  - Black Affairs, President's Council on: Minutes, 1980-1990; 3 folders (Box 110)
  - Black Affairs, President's Council on: Correspondence, 1975-1990 December; 3 folders (Box 111)
  - Black Careers Conference, 1986-1987 (Box 111)
  - Black Cultural Center/Mary Lou Williams Center, 1980-1991 June; 2 folders (Box 111)
  - Black Cultural Center Board of Directors, 1982-1989 (Box 111)
  - Black Graduate Student Alliance, 1985-1991 June (Box 112)
  - Black On White Conference, 1988-1989 (Box 112)
  - Black Student Alliance (formerly: Association Of African Students), 1978-1991 June; 3 folders (Box 112)
  - Bog House (1-2 of 3), 1988-1991 June; 2 folders (Box 112)
  - Bog House (3 of 3), 1988-1991 June (Box 113)
  - Bursar, Office Of, 1983-1988 (Box 113)
  - Bus Service, 1980-1991 June (Box 113)
  - Business & Finance, Office Of, 1981-1991 June; 2 folders (Box 113)
  - Cable TV Duke Uni., 1981-1991 June; 2 folders (Box 113)
  - Calendar Correspondence, 1981-1991 June (Box 113)
  - Campus Services, 1978-1991 June (Box 114)
  - Career Development Center, 1990 July-1991 June (Box 114)
  - Career Development Center Construction, 1987-1990 June; 3 folders (Box 114)
    Includes folded oversize drawings
  - Career Development Center Construction, 1990-1991 June; 3 folders (Box 115)
  - Career Development Center Formation (1-2 of 3), 1985-1990 June; 2 folders (Box 115)
  - Career Development Center Formation (3 of 3), 1985-1990 June (Box 116)
  - Career Development Center Recruitment Policy, 1990 (Box 116)
  - Career Development Coordinating Committee, 1990 July-1991 June (Box 116)
  - Center For Jewish Life Board Of Directors (1 of 3), 1990 (Box 116)
  - Center For Jewish Life Board Of Directors (2-3 of 3), 1990; 2 folders (Box 117)
  - Center For Jewish Life, 1986-1988; 3 folders (Box 117)
  - Chamber Of Commerce Correspondence, 1983-1991 June (Box 117)
  - C.H.A.N.C.E., 1985-1991 June (Box 117)
  - C.H.A.N.C.E., 1986-1987 (Box 198)
    FERPA restricted until 2057.
  - Chanticleer, 1981-1991 June (Box 118)
  - Chapel Correspondence, 1986-1990 June (Box 118)
  - Chapel: Sermons, 1990 (Box 118)
  - Community Service Center, 1988-1991 June; 2 folders (Box 118)
  - Correspondence: Miscellaneous, 1981-1991 June; 2 folders (Box 119)
  - Cultural Affairs Office, 1981 July-1991 June; 2 folders (Box 119)
  - Cultural Services Program Of Medical Center, 1982-1988 (Box 119)
  - Development Office, 1986-1991 June; 2 folders (Box 119)
  - Duke Chapel Development Committee, 1981-1989 (Box 120)
  - Duke Connection, 1984-1985 (Box 120)
  - Duke Dance Group, 1973-1989 (Box 120)
  - East Campus Facilities, 1980-1990 (Box 120)
  - Educational Programs, 1974- 1986 June (Box 120)
  - Experiential Living/Learning Group, 1981-1990 February; 2 folders (Box 120)
  - Experiential Program Institute, 1988 (Box 120)
  - Facilities & Environment Committee on (Academic Facilities Committee), 1981-1989 (Box 120)
  - Facilities Planning & Management, 1980-1991 (Box 121)
  - Federal Surplus Properties, 1975-1984 (Box 121)
  - Film & Video Center, 1985-1992 January (Box 121)
  - Founder's Day, 1981-1990 (Box 121)
  - Freshmen Orientation (1-2 of 3), 1986-1991; 2 folders (Box 121)
  - Freshmen Orientation (3 of 3), 1986-1991 (Box 122)
  - Friends Of Duke Chapel, 1980-1989 (Box 122)
  - Gay & Lesbian Alliance, Duke (DGLA), 1971-1991 June (Box 122)
  - Gifts, 1972-1991 June (Box 122)
  - Gothic Bookshop, 1986-1989 (Box 122)
  - Graduate & Professional Student Association, 1980-1987; 3 folders (Box 122)
  - Graduate & Professional Student Association, 1987-1991 June (Box 123)
  - Graduate & Professional Women's Network, 1986 (Box 123)
  - Graduate School, 1980-1991 June (Box 123)
  - Green Fund Correspondence, 1971-1989 (Box 198)
    FERPA restricted until 2059.
  - Grounds Task Force, 1987-1991 March (Box 123)
  - Gross Receipts Tax, 1972 (Box 123)
  - Health, Physical Education, and Recreation, 1986-1990 September (Box 123)
  - Hertz Rent-a-Car Service, 1975-1980 (Box 123)
  - Hideaway Bar, 1972-1991; 3 folders (Box 123)
  - Institute Of Policy Sciences And Public Affairs, 1981-1989 (Box 124)
  - Institute Of The Arts, 1984-1990 April (Box 124)
  - Insurance: Duke University, 1981-1991 April (Box 124)
  - Insurance Brochures, 1974-1988 (Box 124)
  - Insurance: Employee Blue Cross Blue Shield, 1970-1991 June (Box 124)
  - Insurance Student, 1981-1991 June (Box 124)
  - Insurance Student, 1982-1984 (Box 199)
  - Interfraternity Council, 1979-1991 (Box 124)
  - Interfraternity Council, 1981 (Box 199)
  - International House (1 of 2), 1986-1991 June (Box 124)
  - International House (2 of 2), 1986-1991 June (Box 125)
  - Invitations, 1990-1991 June (Box 125)
  - Invitation Lists (Box 125)
  - Medical Center/School, Duke University, 1981-1990 December (Box 125)
  - Medical Center/School, Duke University, 1983, 1987 (Box 199)
    FERPA restricted until 1987.
  - Men's Crew, 1980-1990 April (Box 125)
    Includes some materials on Women's Crew
  - Missing Link, 1984-1988 January (Box 126)
  - On-campus Recruiting Committee, 1967-1991 January (Box 126)
  - Organizational Charts: UNC, State, UNC-G, etc., 1971-1989 (Box 126)
  - Orientation For Black Students, 1987-1990 (Box 126)
  - Orientation, Other Student Groups, 1979-1990 (Box 126)
  - Outdoor Leaders Program, 1986-1989 (Box 126)
  - Page Box Office, 1983-1991 February (Box 126)
  - Panhellenic Council, 1986-1989 (Box 126)
  - Photography Club Correspondence, 1986-1989 (Box 126)
  - Physical Planning, Department Of, 1982-1989 (Box 127)
  - Pickets And Protests, 1968-1985 (Box 127)
  - Pickets And Protests, 1968 (Box 199)
    FERPA restricted until 2038.
  - Pisces, 1974-1989 (Box 127)
  - Plant Accounting., 1978-1989 (Box 127)
  - Policies: Miscellaneous, 1982-1991 (Box 127)
  - Pornography (X-Rated Films), 1975-1990; 2 folders (Box 127)
  - Pravada, 1980-1991 (Box 128)
  - President's Council, Subcommittee On Faculty Development, 1980 (Box 128)
  - Project Wild, 1986-1991; 2 folders (Box 128)
  - Provost, Office Of, 1986-1991 June; 2 folders (Box 128)
  - Pruett Endowment For Community Interaction, 1989 (Box 128)
  - Quadrangle Pictures, 1983-1990 (Box 128)
  - Race Relations, 1979-1990 June (Box 129)
  - Racism, 1972-1991 June (Box 129)
  - Religious Cults, 1984 (Box 129)
  - Registrar, 1981-1991 June (Box 129)
  - Residence Halls Problems, 1979-1988 (Box 129)
  - Residential Life Task Force (1-2 of 3), 1989-1990; 2 folders (Box 129)
  - Residential Life Task Force (3 of 3), 1989-1990 (Box 130)
  - Residential Life Task Force, 1987 (Box 130)
  - Residential Life Task Force, 1985-1986; 2 folders (Box 130)
  - Residential Life, 1981-1986; 2 folders (Box 130)
  - Residential Life, 1987-1991 June; 2 folders (Box 131)
  - Residential Life Faculty In Residence, 1983-1991 April (Box 131)
  - Residential Life Language Corridors, 1983-1990 February (Box 131)
  - Residential Policy Committee, 1969-1987; 2 folders (Box 131)
  - Residential Programming, 1985-1991 June; 2 folders (Box 132)
  - Residential Staff, 1984-1991 January (Box 132)
  - Resume Book: University Consortium, 1989 (Box 132)
  - ROTC, 1981-1991 January; 2 folders (Box 132)
  - Safety/Security On Campus, 1989; 3 folders (Box 133)
  - Safety/Security on Campus, 1980, 1988 (Box 199)
    FERPA restricted until 2058.
  - Scholarships Correspondence, 1981-1989 March (Box 133)
  - SMP Vs. Duke University, 1988-1991 June (Box x)
    Restricted.
  - Student Affairs Leadership Assistance Program (SALAP, formerly Provost's Agreement), 1986-1991 June (Box 133)
  - Student Affairs Leadership Assistance Program (SALAP, formerly Provost's Agreement), 1986-1991 June (Box 199)
    FERPA restricted until 2061.
  - Student Health Fee, Policies Regarding, 1976-1991 June (Box 133)
  - Student Health Fee, Letters, Waiver Forms, 1976-1990 (Box 134)
  - Student Health Fee, Waiver Problems, 1983-1991 (Box 134)
  - Summer Program: Pre College & TIP, 1979-1980 August (Box 134)
  - Student Organizations (Officers), 1970-1990 June (Box 134)
  - Student Organizations: fundraising Drivers, 1983-1989 June (Box 134)
  - Triangle Substance Abuse Association, 1985-1989 (Box 134)
  - Undergraduate Admissions (1 of 3), 1972-1991 June (Box 134)
  - Undergraduate Admissions (2-3 of 3), 1972-1991 June; 2 folders (Box 135)
  - University Stores, 1980-1990 June (Box 135)
  - University Treasurer, 1979-1988 (Box 135)
  - Vice Presidents Group: Correspondence: Griffith's, 1980-1986; 3 folders (Box 135)
  - Vice Presidents Group: Correspondence: Griffith's, 1986-1991 June; 3 folders (Box 136)
  - Vice Presidents Group: Kiawah Conferences, 1985 (Box 136)
  - Vice Presidents Group: Miscellaneous Mailings (1-2 of 4), 1981-1987; 2 folders (Box 136)
  - Vice Presidents Group: Miscellaneous Mailings (3-4 of 4), 1981-1987; 2 folders (Box 137)
  - Vice Presidents Group: Miscellaneous Mailings, 1986-1990; 4 folders (Box 137)
  - Vice Presidents Group: Miscellaneous, 1987-1991 June; 2 folders (Box 138)
  - Vice Presidents Group: Group Newsletter, 1983-1991 June; 2 folders (Box 138)
  - Vice Presidents Group: Group Prospective Members, 1988-1991 June (Box 138)
  - Visitors, 1971-1989 (Box 138)
  - Volunteer Services, 1983-1990; 2 folders (Box 138)
  - Women's Center, 1982-1988; 2 folders (Box 139)
  - Women's Center: Board Of Directors, 1988-1989 (Box 139)
  - WuDunn Scholarship Fund, 1983-1991 June; 2 folders (Box 139)
    Also includes materials on the Janet Chiang Grant and Scholarship
  - YM/YWCA, 1981, 1990 (Box 139)
- Accessions A93-37, A93-41, A93-49, 11
  This series includes materials from three separate accessions which arrived in the Archives at different times but which together made up a largely alphabetical run of files. The files are primarily alphabetical, with some additional files at the end of the list. Materials include correspondence, reports, memorandums, printed materials, and other material types related to policy development and decisions, fraternity activities and disciplinary actions, the President's Council on Black Affairs, Student Health programs and policies, University Union (now the Bryan Center) policies and activities, student housing, denominational chaplains, and many other topics.
  - Academic Council, 1981-1990 February (Box 139)
  - Academic Council: Governance Committee, 1988-1989 (Box 139)
  - Access (Networking In The Public Interest), 1988-1990 (Box 139)
  - Accounting Code Notices, 1980-1991 (Box 140)
  - Accounting Procedures, 1982-1991 June (Box 140)
  - Afro-American Studies, 1975-1983 (Box 140)
  - Afro-American Studies, 1975-1977 (Box 199)
    Personnel restriction until 2057.
  - Aids Task Force, 1989-1991 March (Box 140)
  - Alcohol & Drug Abuse, before 1991 July; 3 folders (Box 140)
  - Alcohol & Drug Abuse, 1990-1991; 2 folders (Box 141)
  - Alcohol Policy Violations, 1985-1991 February (Box 141)
  - Alcoholic Policy, 1983-1985 (Box 141)
  - Alcoholic Regulations Committee, 1985-1990 April; 2 folders (Box 141)
  - Alumni Affairs, 1972-1990 February (Box 141)
  - Alumni Lounge, 1984-1989 (Box 141)
  - American Dance Festival, 1977-1990; 2 folders (Box 142)
  - Archive, 1972-1989 (Box 142)
  - Articles re: Duke University, 1974-1991 June; 3 folders (Box 142)
  - Artists Series, 1982-1991 May; 2 folders (Box 142)
  - Arts Theme House, 1989-1991 March (Box 143)
  - ASAP, BMI, etc.(Licensing & Royalty Fees), 1978-1988 March (Box 143)
  - ASDU: Student Activities Fees, 1971-1991 June; 2 folders (Box 143)
  - ASDU Abortion Loan, 1981 (Box 143)
  - Asian/Pacific Studies, 1989 (Box 143)
  - Athletic Department: Final Four Activities, 1977- 1991 June (Box 143)
  - Athletic Department, 1987-1991 June; 2 folders (Box 143)
  - Athletic Department: Indoor Stadium, 1976-1990 December (Box 144)
  - Auxiliary Services, 1981-1991 June (Box 144)
  - Baccalaureate Evaluation Committee, 1983-1984 (Box 144)
  - Banks, 1970-1990 October (Box 144)
  - Bargroup Video, 1988-1990 December (Box 144)
  - Bassett Fund Lectures, 1963-1990 January (Box 144)
  - Benches, 1976-1988 November (Box 144)
  - Benefits: DU, 1975-1990 August (Box 144)
  - Benjamin N. Duke Scholarship, 1986-1991 April (Box 144)
  - Mary Duke Biddle Foundation, 1968, 1988-1989 (Box 144)
  - Black Affairs President Council Minutes, 1990-1991 (Box 145)
  - Black Alumni Connection, DU (DUBAC), 1988 (Box 145)
  - Breakfast Club, 1990 (Box 145)
  - Broadway Performances, 1985 Janaury-1991 June (Box 145)
  - Brodie H. Keith, President, 1985-1991 June; 2 folders (Box 145)
  - Bryan University Center, 1986-1991 March (Box 145)
  - Bryan Center Management/Operations, 1981-1991 March; 2 folders (Box 145)
  - Bulletins Of Duke University, 1983-1991 (Box 146)
  - Caps: Counseling & Psy Services, 1986- 1991 June (Box 146)
  - Chapel Bulletins, 1983-1990 October (Box 146)
  - Chaplains: General Correspondence, 1972-1990 (Box 146)
  - Chaplains: Baptist Chaplain, 1975-1984 (Box 146)
  - Chaplains: Black Campus Ministry, 1989 (Box 146)
  - Chaplains: Campus Crusade, 1980-1988 (Box 146)
  - Chaplains: Catholic Chaplain, 1969-1991 (Box 146)
  - Chaplains: Church of Jesus Christ of Latter Day Saints, 1982 (Box 146)
  - Chaplains: Episcopal Chaplain, 1958-1984 (Box 146)
  - Chaplains: Intervarsity Christian Fellowship, 1980-1990 (Box 146)
  - Chaplains: Jewish (1 of 2), 1971-1991 May (Box 146)
  - Chaplains: Jewish (2 of 2), 1971-1991 May (Box 147)
  - Chaplains: Lutheran Chaplain, 1972-1984 (Box 147)
  - Chaplains: Presbyterian Chaplain, 1973-1989 (Box 147)
  - Chaplains: United Campus Christian Fellowship, 1972 (Box 147)
  - Chaplains: United Church of Christ, 1980 (Box 147)
  - Chaplains: United Methodist Chaplain, 1982-1982 (Box 147)
  - Chaplains: United Ministry Chaplain, 1972-1973 (Box 147)
  - Chronicle Board, 1989 July-1991 June (Box 147)
  - Chronicle Board, 1981-1989 June; 3 folders (Box 147)
  - Chronicle Board: By Laws, 1980-1991 June (Box 148)
  - Chronicle Newspaper, 1969-1991 June (Box 148)
  - Coffee House: East Campus, 1981-1991 June (Box 148)
  - Commencement Correspondence, 1980-1991 June; 2 folders (Box 148)
  - Conferences, 1981-1991 June; 2 folders (Box 148)
  - Computers, 1979-1990 December; 2 folders (Box 149)
  - Management Information Systems, 1986-1990 May (Box 149)
  - Conference On Career Choices, 1979-1991 June; 2 folders (Box 149)
  - Consortium On Financing Higher Education (COFHE) (1 of 2), 1979-1989 April (Box 149)
  - Consortium On Financing Higher Education (COFHE) (2 of 2), 1979-1989 April (Box 150)
  - Cox, Dean Richard, Correspondence From, 1975- 1991 June (Box 150)
  - Creative Learning Center, 1989-1991 June (Box 150)
  - Cullins, Maureen, 1988-1991 March (Box 150)
  - Dance Black, 1976-1986 (Box 150)
  - Demonstrations, 1969-1991 January (Box 150)
  - Dean/Officers Council, 1990-1991 (Box 150)
  - Dining Hall Correspondence, 1980-1991; 2 folders (Box 150)
  - Disruption Plan, 1973-1974 (Box 150)
    Emergency plan, or plan for disruption of university activities.
  - The Downunder, 1981-1991 June (Box 150)
    Includes folded architectural drawings.
  - Drama Program, 1982-1990 November; 2 folders (Box 151)
  - Drama Program, 1982-1990 (Box 199)
    Personnel restriction until 2060.
  - Drugs: State Of NC Ratified Bill, 1971-1990 (Box 151)
  - Duke Coalition For Peace (Box 151)
  - Duke Debate, 1982-1991 April; 2 folders (Box 151)